[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "Mankind it mars, speech it hinders, yet speech it will inspire. What is it?",
    "answer": "Ale"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What we caught, we threw away; what we didn't catch, we kept. What did we keep?",
    "answer": "Lice"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Thirty white horses on a red hill: first they champ, then they stamp, then they stand still.",
    "answer": "Teeth"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What do dogs, chocolate, and trees have in common?",
    "answer": "Bark"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "I sizzle like bacon, came from an egg, change shape with my food and haven't one leg.",
    "answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The alphabet goes from A to Z but I go Z to A. What am I?",
    "answer": "Zebra"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The cow is my cousin. If you see my name you'll know what I mean. What am I?",
    "answer": "Moose"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "My start goes on toast, and my end's how birds move. My baby eats leaves but I drink flowers",
    "answer": "Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Where do rabbits go to enjoy their breakfast, lunch and dinner?",
    "answer": "Ihop"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "I am a fruit, a bird and a person. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Kiwi"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "I've got lumps on my back and I live on the sand. I'm strong and I carry you over the land.",
    "answer": "Camel"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What day do chickens fear the most?",
    "answer": "Frydays"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "I'm bigger than a house, scared of a mouse, have great big toes and a hose for a nose.",
    "answer": "Elephant"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "I row with four paddles but never leave home. What am I?",
    "answer": "Turtle"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "I'm covered in feathers, I cluck, and you might get called my name if you're scared.",
    "answer": "Chicken"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Play me with a ball and bat or hear me chirp in a top hat. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Cricket"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "A king without a crown, I sound untruthful but can't talk. What am I?",
    "answer": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "I grow from eye to fish to creature. I burp when I talk and jump when I walk. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Frog"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "A prickly house, the face of a mouse, I'm a ball you can't throw when I spot a foe. What am I?",
    "answer": "Hedgehog"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "I never leave water but I breathe air. I live in a school all my life. What am I?",
    "answer": "Dolphin"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "I have wings, I can fly, I'm not a bird yet I soar through the sky. What am I?",
    "answer": "Airplane"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "I have no eyes, legs or ears but I can move the earth if you give me time. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Worm"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "I have black circles round my eyes even when I'm not tired. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Panda"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "I slither around with my home on my back. I've never been rich but I leave silver tracks.",
    "answer": "Snail"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "I munch leaves from treetops but my feet never leave the ground. What am I?",
    "answer": "Giraffe"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "I join you at parties every year, but I never get to enjoy them. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "I build a home of sticky string and catch my prey with a bite or sting. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Spider"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "I plough fields but never sow, I've a corkscrew tail and snuffly nose",
    "answer": "Pig"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What disappears as soon as you say it's name?",
    "answer": "Silence"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What kind of vegetables are the most fun at parties?",
    "answer": "Fungi"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Why did the citrus tree go to the hospital?",
    "answer": "Lemonaid"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "The more of this there is, the less you see. What am I?",
    "answer": "Darkness"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "The more you take, the more you leave behind. What are they?",
    "answer": "Footsteps"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "If two's company, and three's a crowd, what are four and five?",
    "answer": "Nine"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "I can fill up a room without taking any space what am I?",
    "answer": "Light"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "What has many ears but cannot hear?",
    "answer": "Corn"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "People in poverty have this. If you eat this you will die. What is it?",
    "answer": "Nothing"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "A word I know, six letters it contains, remove one letter and 12 remains, what is it?",
    "answer": "Dozens"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "What did the Mom tomato say to the dawdling Baby tomato?",
    "answer": "Ketchup"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "You bought me for dinner but never eat me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Cutlery"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What kind of apples do computers prefer?",
    "answer": "Macintosh"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What makes more as you take them?",
    "answer": "Footsteps"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "I am an odd number. Take away a letter and I become even. What number am I?",
    "answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Mississippi, Rhine, Amazon, Colorado, Nile, and Rio Grande. What are all of these?",
    "answer": "Rivers"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": " What is easy to get into but hard to get out of?",
    "answer": "Trouble"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": " I go up and down stairs without moving. What am I?",
    "answer": "Carpet"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "What has ten letters and needs gas to start?",
    "answer": "Automobile"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "What five-letter word becomes shorter when you add two letters to it?",
    "answer": "Short"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "David's parents have three sons: Snap, Crackle and...?",
    "answer": "David"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "What word is spelled wrong in the dictionary?",
    "answer": "Wrong"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "I possess a halo of water, walls of stone, and a tongue of wood. Long I have stood; what am I?",
    "answer": "Castle"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "What kind of music is bad for balloons?",
    "answer": "Pop"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "What did the pirate say on this 80th birthday party?",
    "answer": "Ayematey"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "What is no cat birthday party complete without?",
    "answer": "Mewsic"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "What is a tornado's favorite party game?",
    "answer": "Twister"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "What candy has two female pronouns?",
    "answer": "Hersheys"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "What kind of candy does a zombie refuse to eat?",
    "answer": "Lifesavers"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "What kind of candy is never on time?",
    "answer": "Chocolate"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "What is black and sticky?",
    "answer": "Licorice"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "I am the most popular sweet treat given on Valentine's Day. What am I?",
    "answer": "Chocolate"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "Which one of Santa's reindeer can be seen on Valentine's day?",
    "answer": "Cupid"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "Which of Santa's reindeer has the most to learn about politeness?",
    "answer": "Rudeolph"
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "question": "Which one of Santa's reindeer can you see in outer space?",
    "answer": "Comet"
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "question": "What do you call it after all the Christmas gifts have been opened?",
    "answer": "Christmess"
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "question": "I am an egg, but I'm meant to be drunk. What type of egg am I?",
    "answer": "Eggnog"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "question": "Santa Claus will be doing his own laundry. What detergent will he use?",
    "answer": "Yuletide"
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "question": "I am a colored strip used to decorate your tree, metallic and shiny you will find me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Tinsel"
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "question": "What is the name of a runner's favorite reindeer?",
    "answer": "Dasher"
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "question": "What do you call a vampire caught in a blizzard?",
    "answer": "Frostbite"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "question": "When you go out in a blizzard and you see a vampire, what do you get?",
    "answer": "Frostbite"
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "What bites but doesn't have any teeth?",
    "answer": "Frost"
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "question": "What falls at the North Pole but never gets injured?",
    "answer": "Snow"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "question": "Almost everyone needs it, asks for it, gives it, but almost nobody takes it. What is it?",
    "answer": "Advice"
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "question": "What vehicle is spelled the same backwards and forwards?",
    "answer": "Racecar"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "question": "What do you call your dad when he falls through the ice?",
    "answer": "Popsicle"
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "question": "It floats like a log. It looks likes a log. But it isn't a log. What is it?",
    "answer": "Alligator"
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "question": "What is black when you buy it, red when you use it, and white when you are done with it?",
    "answer": "Charcoal"
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "question": "You bought me for dinner but never eat me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Silverware"
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "question": "What do you call a man that doesn't use contraceptives?",
    "answer": "Daddy"
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "question": "If you ask your father, \"What's on the TV,\" what would his answer be?",
    "answer": "Dust"
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "question": "What instrument does a skeleton play?",
    "answer": "Trombone"
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "question": "I know a word of letters three, add two more and less there will be. What word is it?",
    "answer": "Few"
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "question": "I have no feet, no hands, no wings, but I climb to the sky. What am I?",
    "answer": "Smoke"
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "question": "If you drop a yellow hat in the Red Sea, what does it become?",
    "answer": "Wet"
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "question": "I'm found in socks, scarves, and mittens. I'm found in the paws of playful kittens. What am I?",
    "answer": "Yarn"
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "question": "What is at the end of a rainbow?",
    "answer": "W"
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "question": "A box without hinges, key or lid; inside, a golden treasure is hid",
    "answer": "Egg"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "question": "If you took two apples from three apples, how many apples would you have?",
    "answer": "Two"
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "question": "What do you throw out when you want to use it, but take in when you don't want to use it?",
    "answer": "Anchor"
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "question": "What word of five letters has one left when two are removed?",
    "answer": "Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "In the window she sat weeping. And with each tear her life went seeping.",
    "answer": "Candle"
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "question": "If you feed it, it lives, If you water it-it dies!",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "question": "I am so simple, that I can only point, yet I guide men all over the world",
    "answer": "Compass"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "What has hands but can't clap?",
    "answer": "Clock"
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "question": "Give me food and I will live, give me water, and I will die",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "question": "I have a 100 legs but cannot stand. A long neck but no head. And I eat the maids life.",
    "answer": "Broom"
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "question": "The maker doesn't want it. The buyer doesn't use it. The user doesn't know it. What am I?",
    "answer": "Coffin"
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "question": "Four legs up, four legs down, soft in the middle, Hard all around.",
    "answer": "Bed"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "question": "You hear me once, you heard me again, and then I die until I am called again",
    "answer": "Echo"
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "question": "I have no top or bottom but I can hold Flesh, bones and blood all at the same time.",
    "answer": "Ring"
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "question": "How do you spell hard water with three letters?",
    "answer": "Ice"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "Joe's father had three sons: Snap, Crackle and...?",
    "answer": "Joe"
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "Lovely and round, I shine with pale light, grown in the darkness, a lady's delight.",
    "answer": "Pearl"
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "What has many keys but can't open a single lock?",
    "answer": "Piano"
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "I work when I play and play when I work.",
    "answer": "Musician"
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "What gets wetter and wetter the more it dries?",
    "answer": "Towel"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "What runs all around a backyard, yet never moves?",
    "answer": "Fence"
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "Take off my skin - I won't cry, but you will! What am I?",
    "answer": "Onion"
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "What kind of room has no doors or windows?",
    "answer": "Mushroom"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "question": "What is the shortest complete sentence in the English language",
    "answer": "Go"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "question": "What gets broken without being held?",
    "answer": "Promise"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "question": "What is that which belongs to you But others use it more than you do?",
    "answer": "Name"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "question": "What goes up the hill and down the hill, And spite of all, yet standeth still?",
    "answer": "Road"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "question": "What has an eye but can not see?",
    "answer": "Needle"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "question": "What has to be broken before you use it?",
    "answer": "Egg"
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "question": "What goes through cities and fields, but never moves?",
    "answer": "Road"
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "question": "What kind of tree can you carry in your hand?",
    "answer": "Palm"
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "question": "What invention lets you look right through a wall?",
    "answer": "Window"
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "question": "What can travel around the world while staying in a corner?",
    "answer": "Stamp"
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "question": "What Word is represented by this rebus.?",
    "answer": "Summary"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "question": "What has a bottom at the top?",
    "answer": "Legs"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "What is always coming but never arrives?",
    "answer": "Tomorrow"
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "Iron roof, glass walls Burns and burns And never falls.",
    "answer": "Lantern"
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "I am a spring flower that rhymes with hill, if you know my name, tell me you will",
    "answer": "Daffodil"
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "Birds lay these in the spring and it rhymes with legs. What is it?",
    "answer": "Eggs"
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "Name a word thats four letters long, ends in u-n-t and is used to refer to some women?",
    "answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "What wears rings but has no fingers?",
    "answer": "Saturn"
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "What can run but has no legs?",
    "answer": "Watter"
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "What is it flowers do that rhymes with room? ",
    "answer": "Bloom"
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "What five-letter word stays the same when you take away the first, third, and last letter?",
    "answer": "Empty"
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "What eats a lot of iron and yet has no digestion issues?",
    "answer": "Rust"
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "question": "What three letters change a girl into a woman?",
    "answer": "Age"
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "What does a house wear?",
    "answer": "Address"
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "What word is pronounced the same if you take away four of its five letters?",
    "answer": "Queue"
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "A seven letter word containing thousands of letters...what am I?",
    "answer": "Mailbox"
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "What is it that when you take away the whole, you still have some leftover?",
    "answer": "Wholesome"
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "I make a loud sound when I'm changing. When I do change, I get bigger but weigh less. What am I?",
    "answer": "Popcorn"
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "What can run but can't walk?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "Railroad crossing, watch out for cars. Can you spell that without any Rs?",
    "answer": "That"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "What stays in the corner all the time but travels around the world?",
    "answer": "Stamps"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "What starts with a T, ends with a T, and has T in it?",
    "answer": "Teapot"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "What do you call a camel with 4 humps?",
    "answer": "Pregnant"
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "question": "I am a body with a leg, an arm, and a head but I look like I am naked and bare. What am I?",
    "answer": "Skeleton"
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "question": "What did the wrapped baby ghoul cry out?",
    "answer": "Mummy"
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "question": "What's Jason Voorhees favorite desert?",
    "answer": "Iscream"
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "question": "What is a ghost's favorite fruit?",
    "answer": "Booberries"
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "question": "What kind of make up is a ghost's favorite to wear?",
    "answer": "Masscarea"
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "question": "Dracula loves to draw this, as well as, put it in the bank. What is it?",
    "answer": "Blood"
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "question": "What do ghost's like to do on a Saturday night?",
    "answer": "Boogie"
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "question": "What do little ghosts like to play with instead of Frisbees?",
    "answer": "Boomerangs"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "question": "What type of music is a mummy's favorite?",
    "answer": "Wrap"
  },
  {
    "id": 151,
    "question": "What can be sour, sweet, hard or soft all at once?",
    "answer": "Candy"
  },
  {
    "id": 152,
    "question": "What do you call a witch that lives on the beach?",
    "answer": "Sandwitch"
  },
  {
    "id": 153,
    "question": "If you eat me, my sender will eat you. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fishhook"
  },
  {
    "id": 154,
    "question": " What is stronger than steel but can't handle the sun?",
    "answer": "Ice"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "question": "I have many faces, expressions, and emotions, and I am usually right at your fingertips. What am I?",
    "answer": "Emojis"
  },
  {
    "id": 156,
    "question": "Until I am measured, I am not known. Yet how you miss me, When I have flown. What am I?",
    "answer": "Time"
  },
  {
    "id": 157,
    "question": " What ancient invention allows people to see through walls?",
    "answer": "Windows"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "question": "What can go through glass without breaking it?",
    "answer": "Light"
  },
  {
    "id": 159,
    "question": "What word has kst in the middle, in the beginning, and at the end?",
    "answer": "Inkstand"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "question": "I am always hungry and will die if not fed, but whatever I touch will soon turn red. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "question": "What do you call a Hufflepuff with one brain cell?",
    "answer": "Gifted"
  },
  {
    "id": 162,
    "question": "This place has many rooms, including the Great Hall. In 1994 it hosted the Yule Ball. What is it?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "id": 163,
    "question": "Gimme, gimme, gimme candy and give it to me now! Who am I?",
    "answer": "Dudley"
  },
  {
    "id": 164,
    "question": "Beasts I love and kind I am. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "id": 165,
    "question": "What can you catch but not throw?",
    "answer": "Feelings"
  },
  {
    "id": 166,
    "question": "What is worth a billion dollars but comes free of cost?",
    "answer": "Love"
  },
  {
    "id": 167,
    "question": "What is Mrs. Right's first name?",
    "answer": "Always"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "question": "A declaration of love, the beginning of a journey, with vows and a ceremony.",
    "answer": "Marriage"
  },
  {
    "id": 169,
    "question": "I can inflame and ignite a heart with my weapon, so you lovers better watch out. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Cupid"
  },
  {
    "id": 170,
    "question": "What is the end of eternity?",
    "answer": "Y"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "question": "What is another word for joy that starts with H, but for me it starts with U?",
    "answer": "Happiness"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "question": "How do you spell a cute boy with only two letters?",
    "answer": "Qt"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "question": "I am endless, and once you have me you are bound for life. What am I?",
    "answer": "Marriage"
  },
  {
    "id": 174,
    "question": "What four-letter word is the cause of most discord in the world, as well as most cooperation?",
    "answer": "Love"
  },
  {
    "id": 175,
    "question": "I am a nine-lettered word and rhyme with perfection; I am yet another name for love. What am I?",
    "answer": "Affection"
  },
  {
    "id": 176,
    "question": "When you attend a wedding you will see two of me, but I am not human. What am I?",
    "answer": "Rings"
  },
  {
    "id": 177,
    "question": "What do the bird couple call one another?",
    "answer": "Tweetheart"
  },
  {
    "id": 178,
    "question": "What flowers are kissable?",
    "answer": "Tulips"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "question": "What do you call two Italian ants?",
    "answer": "Romance"
  },
  {
    "id": 180,
    "question": "This is a five lettered word and is common in a circle and a ring. What is it?",
    "answer": "Round"
  },
  {
    "id": 181,
    "question": "This important shape starts with an H and ends with E and is a part of a sphere. What is it? ",
    "answer": "Hemisphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 182,
    "question": " It is an attribute of a circle and helps find a circles' perimeter? What is it? ",
    "answer": "Radius"
  },
  {
    "id": 183,
    "question": "This shape starts with E and ends with L; it is the pathway of a heavenly planet. What is it?",
    "answer": "Elliptical"
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "question": "It is round but not a circle; it resembles the shape of a hen's egg?",
    "answer": "Oval"
  },
  {
    "id": 185,
    "question": "It has six sides and is also found in a beehive? What shape is it?",
    "answer": "Hexagon"
  },
  {
    "id": 186,
    "question": " It is a quadrilateral and looks like a kite. What is it?",
    "answer": "Rhombus"
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "question": "It has 6 faces, 12 edges, and 8 vertexes and looks like a dice. What is it?",
    "answer": "Cube"
  },
  {
    "id": 188,
    "question": "It is a 3D shape and is a part of our favorite ice-cream? What is it?",
    "answer": "Cone"
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "question": "It is a 3d shape with 6 faces and 12 edges, but it's not a cube. What is it?",
    "answer": "Cuboid"
  },
  {
    "id": 190,
    "question": "It is round in shape and rhymes with sing, and can be found on a girl's fingers. What shape is it?",
    "answer": "Ring"
  },
  {
    "id": 191,
    "question": " It is a polygon with 3 sides and 3 vertexes. What is it? ",
    "answer": "Triangle"
  },
  {
    "id": 192,
    "question": "This important sign starts with a D and ends with a T and is used in morse code. What is it?",
    "answer": "Dot"
  },
  {
    "id": 193,
    "question": "It is round in shape but not a circle, nor an oval. What is it?",
    "answer": "Sphere"
  },
  {
    "id": 194,
    "question": "It is a mathematical formula and includes all the four basic mathematical operations. What is it?",
    "answer": "Bodmas"
  },
  {
    "id": 195,
    "question": "It starts with an H and ends with an S; it is the longest side of a triangle. What is it?",
    "answer": "Hypotenuse"
  },
  {
    "id": 196,
    "question": "It starts with Q and ends with T; it is related to divisibility. What is it?",
    "answer": "Quotient"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "question": "What is pointless and is a geometrical shape and looks like a plate. What is this shape? ",
    "answer": "Circle"
  },
  {
    "id": 198,
    "question": "It starts with I and end with R and is basically numbers with symbols of + and -. What is it?",
    "answer": "Integer"
  },
  {
    "id": 199,
    "question": "It has 4 equal angles and 4 equal sides. What is it? ",
    "answer": "Square"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "question": " It starts with A and ends with the same, and calculated while painting a wall. What is it?",
    "answer": "Area"
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "Which Pokemon love to visit France?",
    "answer": "Paras"
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "What does Beartic like to eat?",
    "answer": "Bearittos"
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "What did the Pokemon say when he looked through the window?",
    "answer": "Charizard"
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "What do you call a Pokemon who doesn't move very fast?",
    "answer": "Kodwols"
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "Which Pokemon does Dracula like most?",
    "answer": "Koffin"
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "Which pokemon is always in a good mood?",
    "answer": "Happiny"
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "I am a God of pokemon. Nobody ever catched me. If u catched me all the pokemons will die. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Arceus"
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "What do you call a Pokemon that wants to be a police officer?",
    "answer": "Magiccop"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "Where do Haunters go on vacation?",
    "answer": "Maliboo"
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "Which college do Pokemon go to?",
    "answer": "Staru"
  },
  {
    "id": 211,
    "question": "What Pokemon only drinks Hydrogen Peroxide?",
    "answer": "Hooh"
  },
  {
    "id": 212,
    "question": "Which Pokemon can tell you the future?",
    "answer": "Pikahead"
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "question": "Do you know what would look good on me?",
    "answer": "Mew"
  },
  {
    "id": 214,
    "question": "What is the best pokemon?",
    "answer": "Paras"
  },
  {
    "id": 215,
    "question": "Which pokemon do soccer players like the most?",
    "answer": "Goalduck"
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "question": "What do you call a pokemon who likes to eat baked beans?",
    "answer": "Goldbeen"
  },
  {
    "id": 217,
    "question": "What Pokemon do people see in auctions?",
    "answer": "Bidoof"
  },
  {
    "id": 218,
    "question": "Which Pokemon could also be a pirate?",
    "answer": "Arrrrrrbok"
  },
  {
    "id": 219,
    "question": "What do you call a Pikachu that can fix computers?",
    "answer": "Geekachu"
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "question": "What's a Pokemon fan's favorite place to go in France?",
    "answer": "Sara"
  },
  {
    "id": 221,
    "question": "What Pokemon is the best eater?",
    "answer": "Pikachew"
  },
  {
    "id": 222,
    "question": "What do Italian Gourgeist's eat for dinner?",
    "answer": "Spookgetti"
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "question": "What do Haunters send their friends while on vacation?",
    "answer": "Ghostcards"
  },
  {
    "id": 224,
    "question": "What did the Pokemon say when he looked through the window?",
    "answer": "Peekatchoo"
  },
  {
    "id": 225,
    "question": "What's the name of the Pokemon that traveled with Dorothy to Oz?",
    "answer": "Totodile"
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "question": "Where water and liquid waste goes",
    "answer": "Drain"
  },
  {
    "id": 227,
    "question": "I live in oceans, rivers and seas. I float when I'm cold, when I'm hot I'm free.",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "question": "What we use to think",
    "answer": "Brain"
  },
  {
    "id": 229,
    "question": "A spot on your clothes",
    "answer": "Stain"
  },
  {
    "id": 230,
    "question": "Twist your ankle",
    "answer": "Sprain"
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "question": "Large long legged, long necked bird",
    "answer": "Crane"
  },
  {
    "id": 232,
    "question": "A flying vessel of transport",
    "answer": "Plane"
  },
  {
    "id": 233,
    "question": "An ache",
    "answer": "Pain"
  },
  {
    "id": 234,
    "question": "Sparkline with from France",
    "answer": "Champagne"
  },
  {
    "id": 235,
    "question": "A rope made of metal links",
    "answer": "Chain"
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "question": "Fast on my feet, driving dogs mad. My tail flicks when I'm angry, I hum if I'm glad.",
    "answer": "Cat"
  },
  {
    "id": 237,
    "question": "I often have a window, and a stamp, when you need to seal me, make my back damp.",
    "answer": "Envelope"
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "question": "Not fancy",
    "answer": "Plain"
  },
  {
    "id": 239,
    "question": "A type of lettuce",
    "answer": "Romaine"
  },
  {
    "id": 240,
    "question": "I can be all colours or no colour at all, sometimes I'm empty, and others I'm full.",
    "answer": "Glass"
  },
  {
    "id": 241,
    "question": "By moon or sun, I'll always be found, but I am undone if no light is around.",
    "answer": "Shadow"
  },
  {
    "id": 242,
    "question": "It's shorter than all the rest, when you're happy you raise it like it's the best.",
    "answer": "Thumb"
  },
  {
    "id": 243,
    "question": "Opposite of crazy",
    "answer": "Sane"
  },
  {
    "id": 244,
    "question": "Picasso's homeland",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "id": 245,
    "question": "I stand up tall and can be very grand. My secret isn't hidden, it's right at hand.",
    "answer": "Piano"
  },
  {
    "id": 246,
    "question": "Some say I smell but I like to be clean. If you mess with my mud I could get pretty mean.",
    "answer": "Pig"
  },
  {
    "id": 247,
    "question": "In a tree I will move as slow as can be, my name is a sin yet from them I'm free.",
    "answer": "Sloth"
  },
  {
    "id": 248,
    "question": "Can you see me? Usually you can't. I can surround you though, and surround your aunt!",
    "answer": "Gas"
  },
  {
    "id": 249,
    "question": "After a fall, I decide to take over. Then life starts to stall, or starts to grow slower.",
    "answer": "Winter"
  },
  {
    "id": 250,
    "question": "I hide what's real and conceal what's true, at times I bring out the courage in you.",
    "answer": "Makeup"
  },
  {
    "id": 251,
    "question": "Buzzing little hummer, I'm busy all summer. No time to shirk, no man is able to do my work.",
    "answer": "Bee"
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "question": "I like to hop around on my four green feet, but sadly it's my legs, that French people love to eat.",
    "answer": "Frog"
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "question": "Lion's hair",
    "answer": "Mane"
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "question": "I have an eye, but I can't see. You'll run for shelter when you notice me.",
    "answer": "Storm"
  },
  {
    "id": 255,
    "question": "I touch the Earth and sky. If I touch you, you'll probably die.",
    "answer": "Lightning"
  },
  {
    "id": 256,
    "question": "I look very sorry when you feel sad, and I love to look happy if you're feeling glad.",
    "answer": "Mirror"
  },
  {
    "id": 257,
    "question": "I get stamped but no foot is pressed on me. Inside me, you place letters for mail delivery.",
    "answer": "Envelope"
  },
  {
    "id": 258,
    "question": "A warrior in the flowers with a sword, he'll use it if he must, to defend his gold hoard.",
    "answer": "Bee"
  },
  {
    "id": 259,
    "question": "A very small piece of sand",
    "answer": "Grain"
  },
  {
    "id": 260,
    "question": "Linked railway carriages",
    "answer": "Train"
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "question": "A storm with violent whirley winds",
    "answer": "Hurricane"
  },
  {
    "id": 262,
    "question": "An addictive drug",
    "answer": "Cocaine"
  },
  {
    "id": 263,
    "question": "You saw me where I couldn't be, yet often you do see me",
    "answer": "Reflection"
  },
  {
    "id": 264,
    "question": "What eight-letter word remains a word as you keep removing one letter from it?",
    "answer": "Starting"
  },
  {
    "id": 265,
    "question": "What English word has three consecutive double letters?",
    "answer": "Bookkeeper"
  },
  {
    "id": 266,
    "question": "I am the sweetest and most romantic fruit. What am I?",
    "answer": "Honeydew"
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "question": "Alcohol makes me thrive and multiply, yet water will kill me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "question": "What is heavy going forward but not going backward?",
    "answer": "Ton"
  },
  {
    "id": 269,
    "question": "Which word is least like the others? Third, fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh, eighth, or ninth?",
    "answer": "Third"
  },
  {
    "id": 270,
    "question": "Which English word is the odd one out - Stun, Ton, Evil, Letter, Mood, Bad, Snap, Straw?",
    "answer": "Letter"
  },
  {
    "id": 271,
    "question": "If you have me, you want to share me. If you share me, you haven't got me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Secret"
  },
  {
    "id": 272,
    "question": "What fruit is always sad?",
    "answer": "Blueberry"
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "question": "I am a term used to confirm. But take away my front, my face, I become known as human avarice.",
    "answer": "Agreed"
  },
  {
    "id": 274,
    "question": "What do ghosts eat on Halloween?",
    "answer": "Ghoulash"
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "question": "What does a ghost keep in his stable?",
    "answer": "Nightmares"
  },
  {
    "id": 276,
    "question": "What do ghosts use to clean their hair?",
    "answer": "Shamboo"
  },
  {
    "id": 277,
    "question": "Where do baby ghosts go during the day?",
    "answer": "Dayscare"
  },
  {
    "id": 278,
    "question": "I am wrapped, but not a gift yet of great value. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Mummy"
  },
  {
    "id": 279,
    "question": "I am a rock bigger than Venus but smaller than Uranus. What am I?",
    "answer": "Earth"
  },
  {
    "id": 280,
    "question": "What falls but never breaks?",
    "answer": "Dusk"
  },
  {
    "id": 281,
    "question": "I am needed for flight but cannot fly on my own. What am I?",
    "answer": "Feathers"
  },
  {
    "id": 282,
    "question": "How did Ben Franklin feel after discovering electricity?",
    "answer": "Shocked"
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "question": "I'm excellent to taste but horrible to smell. What am I?",
    "answer": "Tongue"
  },
  {
    "id": 284,
    "question": "What chemical element doesn't like to follow? ",
    "answer": "Lead"
  },
  {
    "id": 285,
    "question": "What would you call a bird in winter?",
    "answer": "Brrrrd"
  },
  {
    "id": 286,
    "question": "What do dogs have that no other animal has?",
    "answer": "Puppies"
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "question": "I am a god, a planet, and I can measure heat. What am I?",
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "id": 288,
    "question": "I touch your face. I am in your words. I am a lack of space and beloved by birds. What am I?",
    "answer": "Air"
  },
  {
    "id": 289,
    "question": "Occasionally associated with smelly things, what state of matter am I?",
    "answer": "Gas"
  },
  {
    "id": 290,
    "question": "What is neither water nor land, and is always soaking wet?",
    "answer": "Wetlands"
  },
  {
    "id": 291,
    "question": "What periodic element do pyromaniacs love the most? ",
    "answer": "Arsenic"
  },
  {
    "id": 292,
    "question": "What did the scientist say when he found 2 atoms of helium?",
    "answer": "Hehe"
  },
  {
    "id": 293,
    "question": "I am a gas and line-up with neon. I am also the home of a superhero. What am I? ",
    "answer": "Krypton"
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "question": "When the son of the water returns to the parent, it dies. What is it?",
    "answer": "Ice"
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "question": "I can rush, I can be hot, I can be cold, I can be hard, I can slip through anything. What am I?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 296,
    "question": "What is the most uninteresting of all the periodic elements?",
    "answer": "Boron"
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "question": "What animal lives longest in zoos?",
    "answer": "Turtles"
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "question": "I can be good for you, I can be bad. You can find me all over your body. What am I?",
    "answer": "Bacteria"
  },
  {
    "id": 299,
    "question": "What is a Christian priest's favorite part of physics?",
    "answer": "Mass"
  },
  {
    "id": 300,
    "question": "What element is derived from a Norse god?",
    "answer": "Thorium"
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "question": "I am hard like stone but you can find me on the body. What am I?",
    "answer": "Teeth"
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "question": "If I am 90cm plus half my height, how tall am I?",
    "answer": "180cm"
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "question": "What breaks but never falls?",
    "answer": "Dawn"
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "question": "What did the fox scientist name his laboratory?",
    "answer": "Density"
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "question": "What type of cheese is made backward?",
    "answer": "Edam"
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "question": "What didn't Adam and Eve have that everyone else has?",
    "answer": "Parents"
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "question": "What exists but no-body can enter and is unreachable in life?",
    "answer": "Heaven"
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "question": "What can be lost, but not returned?",
    "answer": "Life"
  },
  {
    "id": 309,
    "question": "What is black and white and is red all over?",
    "answer": "Newspaper"
  },
  {
    "id": 310,
    "question": "What do outlaws eat with their milk?",
    "answer": "Crookies"
  },
  {
    "id": 311,
    "question": "Come up and we go, Go down and we stay.",
    "answer": "Anchor"
  },
  {
    "id": 312,
    "question": "The more you take away, the bigger it gets.",
    "answer": "Hole"
  },
  {
    "id": 313,
    "question": "What is the next letter? W, I, T, N, ..?",
    "answer": "L"
  },
  {
    "id": 314,
    "question": "What is it that is full all day and empty at night?",
    "answer": "Shoes"
  },
  {
    "id": 315,
    "question": "I can be written, I can be spoken, I can be exposed, I can be broken.",
    "answer": "News"
  },
  {
    "id": 316,
    "question": "White and thin, red within, with a nail at the end. What is it?",
    "answer": "Finger"
  },
  {
    "id": 317,
    "question": "Use me well and I am everybody, Scratch my back and I am nobody.",
    "answer": "Mirror"
  },
  {
    "id": 318,
    "question": "What is a pirates favorite word?",
    "answer": "Arrgh"
  },
  {
    "id": 319,
    "question": "What color is the wind?",
    "answer": "Blew"
  },
  {
    "id": 320,
    "question": "I run, yet I have no legs. What am I?",
    "answer": "Nose"
  },
  {
    "id": 321,
    "question": "What is Medusa's favorite cheese?",
    "answer": "Gorgonzola"
  },
  {
    "id": 322,
    "question": "What is dressed when night falls and undressed when day breaks?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 323,
    "question": "What type of drum are you not able to play?",
    "answer": "Conundrum"
  },
  {
    "id": 324,
    "question": "What came out from ONE hole and goes in to TWO holes?",
    "answer": "Farts"
  },
  {
    "id": 325,
    "question": "At night they come without being fetched, and by day they are lost without being stolen.",
    "answer": "Stars"
  },
  {
    "id": 326,
    "question": "What is large, yet never grows; has roots that cannot be seen; is taller than trees?",
    "answer": "Mountain"
  },
  {
    "id": 327,
    "question": " I can run but I cannot walk and thoughts follow me wherever I go.",
    "answer": "Nose"
  },
  {
    "id": 328,
    "question": " I disappear in the dark and appear in the day. You cannot feel me if you touch me. ",
    "answer": "Shadow"
  },
  {
    "id": 329,
    "question": "Made of ten but two are we. Five apart and we are weak. Five together havoc wreak. What am I ?",
    "answer": "Fist"
  },
  {
    "id": 330,
    "question": "Shapeless, I take shape. Unguarded, I escape. Death in excess, death without slake. What am I ?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 331,
    "question": "What is orange and sounds like a parrot?",
    "answer": "Carrot"
  },
  {
    "id": 332,
    "question": "What did the dog say when he sat on sandpaper?",
    "answer": "Ruff"
  },
  {
    "id": 333,
    "question": "What do snowmen eat for breakfast?",
    "answer": "Snowflakes"
  },
  {
    "id": 334,
    "question": "How does the lion like his steak done?",
    "answer": "Rawr"
  },
  {
    "id": 335,
    "question": "What kind of corn starts with the letter A?",
    "answer": "Corn"
  },
  {
    "id": 336,
    "question": "Whats a sheep's favorite game?",
    "answer": "Baadminton"
  },
  {
    "id": 337,
    "question": "What is made of holes but can hold water?",
    "answer": "Sponge"
  },
  {
    "id": 338,
    "question": "Where do cow's go on holiday?",
    "answer": "Mooritius"
  },
  {
    "id": 339,
    "question": "How does the grim reaper like his coffee?",
    "answer": "Black"
  },
  {
    "id": 340,
    "question": "What do you call bears with no ears?",
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 341,
    "question": "What do basketballers also dunk other than a basketball?",
    "answer": "Donuts"
  },
  {
    "id": 342,
    "question": "Which sports do bats prefer to play?",
    "answer": "Baseball"
  },
  {
    "id": 343,
    "question": "What round, red veggie are all the other vegetables afraid of?",
    "answer": "Beatroot"
  },
  {
    "id": 344,
    "question": "What's a soccer player's favorite color?",
    "answer": "Goald"
  },
  {
    "id": 345,
    "question": "I have no head, but I have an ear. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Corn"
  },
  {
    "id": 346,
    "question": "What kitchen implement are eggs most afraid of?",
    "answer": "Eggbeaters"
  },
  {
    "id": 347,
    "question": "What do you call Clark Kent with diarrhea?",
    "answer": "Pooperman"
  },
  {
    "id": 348,
    "question": "What is Thor's favorite food?",
    "answer": "Thortillas"
  },
  {
    "id": 349,
    "question": "What is Doc Ock's favorite month?",
    "answer": "Ocktober"
  },
  {
    "id": 350,
    "question": "I swing from webs and can shoot them from my hands. Who am I?",
    "answer": "Spiderman"
  },
  {
    "id": 351,
    "question": "Who is the sassiest supervillain?",
    "answer": "Sassquatch"
  },
  {
    "id": 352,
    "question": "What is Spider-Man's favorite month?",
    "answer": "Webruary"
  },
  {
    "id": 353,
    "question": "What would you find in Superman's bathroom?",
    "answer": "Superbowl"
  },
  {
    "id": 354,
    "question": "What do you get if you cross the man of steel with a hot vegetable broth?",
    "answer": "Souperman"
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "question": "What superhero plays baseball?",
    "answer": "Batman"
  },
  {
    "id": 356,
    "question": "In what month was Dr. Octavius born?",
    "answer": "October"
  },
  {
    "id": 357,
    "question": "If April showers bring May flowers, then what do May flowers bring?",
    "answer": "Pilgrims"
  },
  {
    "id": 358,
    "question": "What do you call a turkey on the day after Thanksgiving?",
    "answer": "Lucky"
  },
  {
    "id": 359,
    "question": "This key has legs, but can't open a door. What is it?",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "id": 360,
    "question": "What is that favorite sport of pumpkins and gourds?",
    "answer": "Squash"
  },
  {
    "id": 361,
    "question": "What is hard, odd shaped and being good fortune on Thanksgiving? ",
    "answer": "Wishbone"
  },
  {
    "id": 362,
    "question": " It's a flower, but it doesn't bloom; it sounds like a month and float over water. What is it?",
    "answer": "Mayflower"
  },
  {
    "id": 363,
    "question": "If we feel scared on Halloween, and jolly on Christmas, then what do we feel on Thanksgiving?",
    "answer": "Stuffed"
  },
  {
    "id": 364,
    "question": "I am orange but not citrus. I am most popular during fall. What am I? ",
    "answer": "Pumpkin"
  },
  {
    "id": 365,
    "question": "What is the name of the cranberry that isn't happy?",
    "answer": "Blueberry"
  },
  {
    "id": 366,
    "question": "It has ears but it cannot hear and it has flakes but it has no hair. What is it?",
    "answer": "Corn"
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "question": "When you buy me I am costly, but the only use I have is just hanging. What am I?",
    "answer": "Earrings"
  },
  {
    "id": 368,
    "question": "You'll find me in a bee, in a comb, in cakes, in a bunch, in a bun and even in mustard. What am I?",
    "answer": "Honey"
  },
  {
    "id": 369,
    "question": "If your aunt ran off to get married, what would you call her?",
    "answer": "Antelope"
  },
  {
    "id": 370,
    "question": "Hard or soft, whole or broken, heavy or light, keep it or give it. What is this?",
    "answer": "Heart"
  },
  {
    "id": 371,
    "question": "Sweet, sour, tart, and sugary, you can see me in every store and in every pantry. What am I?",
    "answer": "Candy"
  },
  {
    "id": 372,
    "question": "When it comes to me, you go on red and stops on green. What am I?",
    "answer": "Watermelon"
  },
  {
    "id": 373,
    "question": "Its ready to walk when I'm all tied up, but really should stop when I'm untied. What am I?",
    "answer": "Shoes"
  },
  {
    "id": 374,
    "question": "Always in you, Sometimes on you; If I surround you, I can kill you. What am I?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 375,
    "question": "When you have me more, you can see only less. What Am I?",
    "answer": "Darkness"
  },
  {
    "id": 376,
    "question": "I am not alive but I grow. I don't have lungs but I need air. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 377,
    "question": "Wash it and it isn't clean. Don't wash it and then it's clean. What I Am?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 378,
    "question": "I'm tall when I'm young, I'm short when I'm old. What am I?",
    "answer": "Pencil"
  },
  {
    "id": 379,
    "question": "I have a bed but I never sleep. I have a mouth but I never speak. What am I?",
    "answer": "River"
  },
  {
    "id": 380,
    "question": "If I drink, I die. If i eat, I am fine. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "id": 381,
    "question": "People make me, save me, change me, raise me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Money"
  },
  {
    "id": 382,
    "question": "Where do snowmen put their money?",
    "answer": "Snowbanks"
  },
  {
    "id": 383,
    "question": "What kind of androids do you find in the Arctic?",
    "answer": "Snobots"
  },
  {
    "id": 384,
    "question": "What is a mountain's favorite type of candy?",
    "answer": "Snowcaps"
  },
  {
    "id": 385,
    "question": "What vegetable was forbidden on the ships of Arctic explorers?",
    "answer": "Leeks"
  },
  {
    "id": 386,
    "question": "How do mountains stay warm?",
    "answer": "Snowcaps"
  },
  {
    "id": 387,
    "question": "What did the police officer say when he saw the snowman stealing?",
    "answer": "Freeze"
  },
  {
    "id": 388,
    "question": "What do snowmen eat for lunch?",
    "answer": "Icebergers"
  },
  {
    "id": 389,
    "question": "What do you call a penguin in the Sahara desert?",
    "answer": "Lost"
  },
  {
    "id": 390,
    "question": "I am a dreamlike fairyland but I can be horrific to many when I cover the land with ice. What am I?",
    "answer": "Winter"
  },
  {
    "id": 391,
    "question": "I am a place where you can find a syrup farm, geese, snow, even loonies and toonies. What am I?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "id": 392,
    "question": "What did the seal say when it swam into a concrete wall?",
    "answer": "Dam"
  },
  {
    "id": 393,
    "question": "What do you call a ghost in the winter?",
    "answer": "Caspbrrrrr"
  },
  {
    "id": 394,
    "question": "What do Snowmen call their offspring?",
    "answer": "Chilldren"
  },
  {
    "id": 395,
    "question": "What do you call an old snowman?",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "id": 396,
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a snowman with a vampire?",
    "answer": "Frostbite"
  },
  {
    "id": 397,
    "question": "What do you call a gangsta snowman?",
    "answer": "Frozet"
  },
  {
    "id": 398,
    "question": "What kind of math do Snowy Owls like?",
    "answer": "Owlgebra"
  },
  {
    "id": 399,
    "question": "What did Frosty the Snowman and Elvira name their baby?",
    "answer": "Frostbite"
  },
  {
    "id": 400,
    "question": "If the sun shines while it's snowing, what should you look for?",
    "answer": "Snowbows"
  },
  {
    "id": 401,
    "question": "What is cold and bites but no teeth?",
    "answer": "Frostbite"
  },
  {
    "id": 402,
    "question": "Which word can be placed between the two following words to make two new ones: TABLE - - - - HOUSE",
    "answer": "Ware"
  },
  {
    "id": 403,
    "question": "Who plays when he works and works when he plays?",
    "answer": "Actor"
  },
  {
    "id": 404,
    "question": "A dragon's tooth in a mortal's hand, I kill, I maim, I divide the land. What am I?",
    "answer": "Sword"
  },
  {
    "id": 405,
    "question": "What has 3 feet but no toes?",
    "answer": "Yardstick"
  },
  {
    "id": 406,
    "question": "Goes over all the hills and hollows, Bites hard, but never swallows. What is it?",
    "answer": "Frost"
  },
  {
    "id": 407,
    "question": "I walk on 4 legs when I was little, 2 legs when I was strong, and 3 legs when I was old. What am I?",
    "answer": "Human"
  },
  {
    "id": 408,
    "question": "What word contains all of the twenty-six letters?",
    "answer": "Alphabet"
  },
  {
    "id": 409,
    "question": "A man shaves several times a day, yet he still has a beard. Who is this man?",
    "answer": "Barber"
  },
  {
    "id": 410,
    "question": "What is the musical part of a turkey?",
    "answer": "Drumstick"
  },
  {
    "id": 411,
    "question": "I am always in front of you, but yet I am never here. What am I?",
    "answer": "Future"
  },
  {
    "id": 412,
    "question": "Where did the baseball keep its lemonade?",
    "answer": "Pitcher"
  },
  {
    "id": 413,
    "question": "If lightning strikes an orchestra, who is most likely to get hit?",
    "answer": "Conductor"
  },
  {
    "id": 414,
    "question": "I begin your sentences. What am I?",
    "answer": "Capital"
  },
  {
    "id": 415,
    "question": "Which word does not belong in the following list: Stop cop mop chop prop shop or crop?",
    "answer": "Or"
  },
  {
    "id": 416,
    "question": "I pass before the sun, yet make no shadow. I'm all around you, but you cannot see me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Wind"
  },
  {
    "id": 417,
    "question": "I am alive without breath and cold as death. I am never thirsty but always drinking. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fish"
  },
  {
    "id": 418,
    "question": "What's 3/7 chicken, 2/3 cat, and 2/4 goat?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "id": 419,
    "question": "I ask no questions, but receive a lot ofs. What am I?",
    "answer": "Doorbell"
  },
  {
    "id": 420,
    "question": "You have to travel far before you turn it over. What is it?",
    "answer": "Odometer"
  },
  {
    "id": 421,
    "question": "Fashions change, but what can a person wear that is never out of style?",
    "answer": "Smile"
  },
  {
    "id": 422,
    "question": "What do people spend a lot of money on it every year, but never want to use it?",
    "answer": "Insurance"
  },
  {
    "id": 423,
    "question": "Roast, boast, coast, post. What do you put in a toaster?",
    "answer": "Bread"
  },
  {
    "id": 424,
    "question": "I have roots nobody sees. I am taller than trees Up, Up I go but I never grow. What am I?",
    "answer": "Mountain"
  },
  {
    "id": 425,
    "question": "I'm where yesterday follows today. And tomorrow's in the middle. What am I?",
    "answer": "Dictionary"
  },
  {
    "id": 426,
    "question": "Lighter than what I am made of. More of me is hidden than seen. What am I?",
    "answer": "Iceberg"
  },
  {
    "id": 427,
    "question": "What color can you eat?",
    "answer": "Orange"
  },
  {
    "id": 428,
    "question": "Where do fish keep their money?",
    "answer": "Riverbank"
  },
  {
    "id": 429,
    "question": "What word is right when pronounced wrong, but is wrong when pronounced right?",
    "answer": "Wrong"
  },
  {
    "id": 430,
    "question": "What insect does a blacksmith manufacture?",
    "answer": "Firefly"
  },
  {
    "id": 431,
    "question": "I am easy to waste. I am unstoppable. What am I?",
    "answer": "River"
  },
  {
    "id": 432,
    "question": "What is difference between a poorly dressed man on a bike, and a well dressed man on a unicycle?",
    "answer": "Attire"
  },
  {
    "id": 433,
    "question": "What can you lose that will cause other people to lose theirs too?",
    "answer": "Temper"
  },
  {
    "id": 434,
    "question": "I'm a kind of cup that doesn't hold water, but makes a lot of noise repeatedly. What am I?",
    "answer": "Hiccup"
  },
  {
    "id": 435,
    "question": "A butcher is 6 feet tall and wears size 12 shoes. What does he weigh?",
    "answer": "Meat"
  },
  {
    "id": 436,
    "question": "It's colorful. No one can reach it, not even the queen. What is it?",
    "answer": "Rainbow"
  },
  {
    "id": 437,
    "question": "Who keeps the ocean clean?",
    "answer": "Mermaid"
  },
  {
    "id": 438,
    "question": "Born of sorrow, grows with age, you need a lot to be a sage. What is it?",
    "answer": "Wisdom"
  },
  {
    "id": 439,
    "question": "I have keys but no locks. I have space but no room. You can enter but can't go outside What am I?",
    "answer": "Keyboard"
  },
  {
    "id": 440,
    "question": "What can go up a chimney down but can't go down a chimney up?",
    "answer": "Umbrella"
  },
  {
    "id": 441,
    "question": "My ring are not worth much but they do tell my age. What am I?",
    "answer": "Tree"
  },
  {
    "id": 442,
    "question": "What common English word has the 3 letter consecutive sequence, \"XOP\"?",
    "answer": "Saxophone"
  },
  {
    "id": 443,
    "question": "You can see me in water, but I never get wet. What am I?",
    "answer": "Reflection"
  },
  {
    "id": 444,
    "question": "What goes up and down, but does not move?",
    "answer": "Staircase"
  },
  {
    "id": 445,
    "question": "It's in your hand though you can not feel it. Only you and time can reveal it. What is it?",
    "answer": "Fate"
  },
  {
    "id": 446,
    "question": "What goes around the wood but never goes into the wood?",
    "answer": "Bark"
  },
  {
    "id": 447,
    "question": "What do you get when you mix lemons with gun powder?",
    "answer": "Lemonades"
  },
  {
    "id": 448,
    "question": "What familiar word starts with IS, ends with AND, and has LA in the middle.",
    "answer": "Island"
  },
  {
    "id": 449,
    "question": "What five-letter word can be read the same upside down or right side up?",
    "answer": "Swims"
  },
  {
    "id": 450,
    "question": "Once you know it exists, it no longer exists. What is it?",
    "answer": "Surprise"
  },
  {
    "id": 451,
    "question": "What goes through a door but never goes in and never comes out?",
    "answer": "Keyhole"
  },
  {
    "id": 452,
    "question": "I can make arrows fly. I can make kites soar. What am I?",
    "answer": "String"
  },
  {
    "id": 453,
    "question": "It files around all day but never goes anywhere? What is it?",
    "answer": "Flag"
  },
  {
    "id": 454,
    "question": "If there are five apples and you take away three, how many apples do you have?",
    "answer": "Three"
  },
  {
    "id": 455,
    "question": "What tastes better than it smells?",
    "answer": "Tongue"
  }
]